(Amy:)Sheldon.
(Raj:)It's okay.
I-I'm not leaving your world.
(Leonard:)I'm just talking
about living across the hall.
(Sheldon:)I understand.
(Sheldon:)Either way,
I want you to know that...
(Sheldon:)I'm aware of how difficult
I can be.
(Sheldon:)So I just want
to say...
(Penny:)thank you
for putting up with me.
(Howard:)Buddy...
(Penny:)How are you guys
getting alo...?
(Penny:)What? Why are
there tears?
(Leonard:)Everything's fine.
(Leonard:)We just started talking
about living arrangements.
(Amy:)Are you crazy? You know
he's a flight risk.
(Sheldon:)That's exactly
what I told him.
(Penny:)Sheldon, we know this
is a sensitive subject,
(Penny:)and Leonard's not gonna
move out until you're ready.
(Sheldon:)Well, what if you did it
gradually?
(Penny:)All right. Well...
(Leonard:)how about we start
with two nights a week
(Leonard:)I live with Penny?
(Sheldon:)How about one night and...